what is the exact step-by-step strategic
process to make more than you do at a
corporate job while only having to work
10 to 15 hours a week I'm going to give
that to you in this video and this is
not just going to be another one of
those videos with mindset and what you
got to do between your brain to get
started there's a podcast that I have
that's going live on Tuesday that's
actually going to cover the mindset
piece that goes along with what I'm
going to talk about here today but for
those of you that have not met me yet my
name is Jeremiah Kowski and I have been
in the coaching mentoring industry for
the last 21 years have built multiple
companies over $10 million a year and I
help people that are getting started a
lot of them how to leave their corporate
job to sell online courses build
memberships and have consistent revenue
between 5 and $25,000 per month that's
about where a lot of our clients fall
into as far as the results very quickly
after working with us but then a lot of
them also go beyond and even make
multiple six figures and even seven
figures in my own business I've made a
quarter of a million dollars a year for
over the last 10 years and my business
is now a seven fig company and so I want
to share with you what I had to do when
I left working corporate as well as what
the strategy is that got me to six
figures and then seven figures this
might not apply to everybody but I think
if I share some of my story with you I
think it's going to really help so what
did I do when I stopped work working for
other companies well I went out there
and I actually started working for other
companies let me explain this is I took
my skill set for my corporate job and
what I did was instead of clocking in 30
to 40 hours a week most of the time I
only ever really clocked in at 30 hours
a week I was on salary and I negotiated
where I didn't have to be on on call for
more than 25 to 30 hours a week so
already I've had time freedom for over a
decade even when I was working at
companies the companies that we building
that we're making over $10 million a
year that I was CEO of okay so what I
want to share with you though is prior
to that what was I doing before I was a
CEO of a $10 million a year profit
company I was doing video editing I was
doing marketing funnels lead gen all the
stuff that I coach and Mentor a lot of
people on I was building actively for
the companies that I worked for and they
were making a consider considerable
amount of profit off of this what I did
was I observed what are the skill sets
that I don't have today that the CEOs of
these companies have and this is
something that I did from day one when I
started working at at a job my first job
officially well well I was working for
my M my mom's business years ago she had
an e-commerce company that was kind of
in our basement type of a thing she was
making millions in our basement which is
amazing but I was basically doing the
shipping and packing but my like outside
of that actually went and worked with a
company their name was Danny johnson.com
they're still in business to this day
and I helped them do a lot of their
their uh video editing as well as then
transitioned into marketing they almost
there was a conversation that I had I
remember this where they they were like
in talks with hey we might need to have
a different CEO of the company you might
be in a position where you could rise up
into the and I was like whoa that's
amazing but then I also kind of didn't
want to do that cuz I kind of wanted to
start my own thing and I kind of wanted
to go off into a different direction
which now looking back I see that but I
didn't recognize it back then so what
always did was I observed what are the
CEOs of the companies that I'm working
for or that I know doing and what skills
do they have that I don't possess today
so there's always going to be a skills
Gap okay and you could literally know
everything I knew everything of what it
takes to build a $20 million a year
company one of the companies I built was
$20 million a year and I knew exactly
what it takes to get there but when it
goes to doing it in my own business and
this
I there's a lot of stuff that I didn't
know how to do that I have had to learn
that you just like until you're in the
weeds of founding a company you don't
know it and and I used to get angry when
people would say this Gary vaynerchuk
used to say this all the time he's like
listen there's a difference between you
know being an employee that grows a
company inside of a company but you
don't have any risk so I knew how to
grow companies without taking risk but
when it actually came to taking risk on
my own was very very risk averse
struggled to do that and because of my
risk averseness because Safety and
Security was such an important thing to
me I always had ended up working for
other people or making way less than my
potential as far as that goes until the
last like year or so I I made a a multi6
fig income and and then we catapulted to
seven figures when I realized what I
didn't know gained the skills and
finally started applying what I learned
over the last 21 years now can I tell
you today like oh do this and you'll be
a
millionaire probably could walk you
through that process if I was coaching
you over the course of a year or two um
but my I'm more I'm more uh suited for
like how do you go from zero to making
that first quarter of a million does
that make sense so that's why I'm like
I'm really hyper qualified I could roll
out of bed tell you everything that it
takes to get to that level and that's
really what my Niche is as far as that
goes a lot of people say well how do you
find your Niche well you got to figure
out what are you super good at that you
could roll out of bed that's actually
kind of boring to you to talk about I'm
be honest with y'all it's kind of boring
for me to talk about this
stuff I just I know it so well it's like
it's so inside of me that I don't have
to think when I'm teaching it and and
yet the quality is at a Mastery level
when I'm sharing it does that make sense
so when it comes to what you're going to
do to actually build your business you
really want to start a establishing
Mastery level skill sets and I can
guarantee you if you are over the age of
30 right now watching this if you're
under the age of 30 you you can totally
do this as well but a lot of people that
I work with are over the age of 30 I
guarantee you if you're over the age of
30 that you got something that you have
mastered over the last 10 15 years since
you were 15 years old that you just you
know how to do better than 99% of any
body that you meet okay you can build a
business around that because then all
you got to do is you got to go find the
other 99% of people and sell them the
thing that you know how to do whether it
be information or a service and so those
are really the two best ways to start
when it comes to uh building a business
when you're when you're leaving a
corporate job is you either you pick one
of these two lanes you either do a
service
okay or you can do
uh
info SL Consulting and I'll tell you
this you can make way more money over
here than over here okay but initially
you may have to actually do this and
this is kind of a springboard to get you
over here and what this is is this is
where you're working in your business
this is where you're working on your
business today I'm at this stage where I
get paid to talk I get paid to open my
mouth I get paid for my ideas I had
great ideas by the way 15 years ago they
were incredible my ideas today are are
are are refined but the but the core of
them are are are pretty much the same as
what they have been for the last 15
years but they've gotten better they
have improved I've gotten better at
explaining them to people as well which
is why now I can get paid more because
it takes me less time to explain this
stuff to people okay when it comes to
service-based
stuff this is you doing the work for
people okay and and there really is a
Gap right here between service-based and
information as far as this goes so I
help a lot of people generally go from
doing a service to monetizing their
knowledge information and skill set so
where that they're not doing Services
they're not actively necessarily doing
the work for people but they're able to
get paid for their information and that
is a a very unique skill set to do
especially to sell to people that you're
going to give them information versus do
it for them it's 10 times easier to sell
somebody on a
service than it is on how to do the
service themselves or how to hire a team
to do the service themselves okay so you
got to understand that aspect of it
either of these is a great place to
start when it comes to leaving a
corporate job so for me I actually went
the services route I ran ads for people
I created their landing pages I created
their marketing and I didn't charge very
much money for this my goal was how do I
get my income up to a quar million
dollars a year as quick as possible cuz
that's what I was making working for
others in one job so what I did was I
literally I
got eight
clients all at different levels one
client was at $2,000 a month another
client was at $5500 a month another one
was at $88,000 a month one was at $1,000
a month and then I think I had I think I
had two more that were at like a th000
as as well so and and so these were like
barebones level I'm just going to run
your ads right
here they didn't have a big budget I
went above and beyond for them though
and I realized that running ads for
people was something that I don't want
to do because it's so timec consuming to
actually get it to work you have to do
way more than just run the ads and
because of my own Integrity of needing
things to actually produce results when
I sell them to people and making sure
that when people buy something from me
actually get what they pay for I was
literally giving a $5500 a month level
service to people that were only paying
me 1,000 bucks a month but overall we
were making a good decent quarter of a
million dollar income off of this I know
that's only six but I had Al alternated
a few of them as far as that goes I know
I had eight clients that I had kind of
rotated during a couple of years after I
left working for somebody else I just
ended up splitting my time into this
here's the problem though you want to
know how many hours I was working doing
that
about 110 hours a
week okay so I was working 35 hours a
week maybe 30 hours a week 25 to 30
hours a week at a job making a quarter
million running my own business I was
working
110 because what I did was I pretty much
was literally still doing exactly the
same processes that I was at my job but
doing this that wasn't sustainable
luckily I didn't have kids I was newly
married and and you know quite frankly
uh that worked out well for my wife and
I it worked out well for us to kind of
have that sort of Separation as far as
that goes where I was I was working from
home which was kind of cool but um like
I was so just focused on our work and
she just kind of had her own life and
that was our first couple of years of
marriage was that and it worked for us
but then when we decided hey I want to
start a family and now we have kids we
have a second one on the
way that doesn't work does that make
sense so I have had to transition
completely away from doing Services
entirely to where now I
work 10 10 to I would say 10 to 20 hours
a week some weeks I work 20 hours a week
but 10 to 15 hours 20 hours a week doing
information Consulting coaching
speaking looking over somebody's
business giving assessment giving
analysis on how to do that okay so what
you got to look at is what are the skill
sets that you have how can you help
people what do you know how to do better
than most people and then you got to
figure out how to monetize that and it
starts by creating what is called an
offer okay so an offer what is an
offer an offer is I'm going to offer you
to do this service for you I'm going to
offer you to build your landing page run
ads and get people to register for your
live event I'm going to create an offer
where I'm going to build your website
for you I'm going to run ads with you
I'm going to consult with your team and
we're going to get enrollments into your
University by the way this is exactly
what I
did and we and we helped like two to 3x
almost all of our clients one of our
clients right here this one that was
$88,000 a month was really cool that was
uh that was Rick Pino we helped him go
from zero to making a million dollar a
month with his worship coach platform
and you can you can literally see it
over here if you go to worship coach
uh.com we helped him build all of this
out all the marketing this is all the
this is all stuff that I had built out
with with him and for him during this
time and we built this business to over
a million dollars a month mentoring
people and like Rave client reviews
they're just like this is the best stuff
on the planet you know people love it
people loved it it was incredible
okay but I did that with a number of
different people but I had to transition
away from doing
services in order to reduce my working
hours so that I could work that 10 to 20
hours a week so what does that actually
look like well again I talked about this
in my previous video last the other week
about how I only work 10 to 15 hours a
week boundaries is important you got to
have boundaries you got to be willing to
say no and walk away from even good
ideas that can pay you money simply
because you're setting standards for
what you're willing to do and you're
going to literally have to transform
into somebody who says that's what I do
now I work 10 to 15 hours a week and
that's what people pay me
for and you have to have an offer that
is irresistible that people sign up for
that they pay you for and so what you
have to learn how to do is you have to
learn the skill
set of in all of
this the skill set of number
one
finding
people who have
problems
okay finding people who are struggling
with something
that you can do a service for of some
kind whether it be dog walking whether
it be hair
care whether it be
cooking whether it be gardening whether
it be G glass
blowing and you can find the people that
they want to learn this or they're
looking for the thing that you are
offering so you have to be able to find
those people and you want them to be
able to find you you want to create a
synergistic connection where yall
connect as far as that goes then what
you have to do is you have to actually
present those people with an offer and
this is where 95% of people fail right
here they don't know how to present an
offer in a way that gets people to buy
it they say okay here's what I offer and
9 times out of 10 not actually 99 times
out of 100 the person says no because
the presentation was off and the
presentation has nothing to do with
necessarily how it looks or how
everything is put together or all of
that or even product quality as far as
that goes I'll tell you that product
quality is important what you offer is
important what you say is
important but this is about the initial
once they find
you how do you bridge the
connection to the fact that if they pay
you money they are going to get a result
okay okay and then number three you have
to
close the
sale okay so learning how to close sales
is the skill set that you have to learn
this is what I Mentor people on right
here is these three
steps this is exactly what I work with
with people inside of my business every
single week in my client growth
accelerator program my coaching program
which you cannot enroll in right now
there is a waiting list for it this is
the only program we have we don't have
other courses or things like that
sometimes we have live events that you
might see us advertise or Market on my
social media make sure to go follow my
social media make sure to subscribe to
this channel okay to get updates for
when we open the doors to the
accelerator get on my email list on my
newsletter you can literally go here go
grab the waiting list jump on that
waiting list and you will get updated
when we open an enrollment period for
this and what we do is we work with you
through how to actually do these three
steps I come alongside you and walk you
through that okay now back to what we're
talking about here though I'm going to
break down for you how to actually do
these three steps right now by the end
of this video and so listen those of you
that are still watching you are about to
get a gold mine right now something that
is like I want you to take notes lean
lean forward if you don't have time to
pay attention to what I'm about to talk
about I want you to save this video come
back to it and many of you you're going
to write down this point in time about
18 minutes into the video where you are
going to bookmark that and you're going
to watch back through this because this
is going to be your strategic process
that you're going to do and many of you
I truly believe after watching this
video you are going to work with me and
our community to implement this as well
inside of my acceler program and join a
lot of our different events as well as
watching the other videos that we have
if you have any questions about any
other topics that You' love to see me
share if you want me to make other
videos for Stuff leave it in the
comments below let me know as as stuff
and ideas start to come up just write a
little comment below this video about
what you would like me to share okay so
step number one how do we go about
finding these people
okay you need to
have
a track traffic
Source okay so again what is traffic
well let's think about this if you're
right if you're if you're in
traffic driving in traffic there are
cars that are driving and hopefully
maybe you're in one of these Corvette
right that'd be
nice you're you're you're in
traffic because there are there are
people there are other human beings that
are going from one destination to
another another and so what you have to
do is you have to take
people that are on platforms like
Instagram like
YouTube like Facebook as well as other
social media platforms and move them
over to your email
list
and optionally a text message SMS list
okay so you want to move people people
from these
platforms over to an email list to find
out how to contact them what is their
contact
information how do you text them as far
as this goes and why would they give you
this information what you're going to do
is you're going to actually bribe them
for it okay so you bribe people
ethically to give you that information
by creating something of value that
solves that problem that they have that
you can do better than anybody else and
so this is where we create an offer and
it becomes an offer and there are many
different stages of offers there can be
an offer that is just for exchange of an
email address and text
message and and and what it is is that
you want you still nowadays because of
AI and by the way AI is incredible I
love it I use it all the time highly
recommend it for brainstorming and
you've been learning information
processing information helps you with
your marketing they just make GPT 4
available for free now that's incredible
over at chat GPT the highest quality AI
on the planet is now available for free
to everybody and that's huge okay I'm
all about it I'm all for AI I'll teach
you how to use that we teach our our our
our students how to use AI in a powerful
way not in a way that gives up their
voice not in a way that replaces them
but in a way that actually amplifies and
increases
their own mindset their own thoughts and
their own ideas so that you are actually
fully generating original thoughts and
ideas but you're using the AI to help
you refine it and come up with those
ideas as far as that goes and if you
follow that process you will actually
start thinking better talking better
communicating better by learning how to
do this this type of stuff so your goal
is traffic Source there are people that
will buy your
service or your Consulting or coaching
or a membership with you or a course
that exists on these different social
media platforms
okay so what you want to do is you want
to get those people to give you their
contact information in exchange for
something of value that solves an
immediate need or problem that they have
now how do you figure out what those
immediate needs or problems are that
people have you need to read their mind
essentially not like in a weird like you
know psychic kind of way okay but you
actually can do so by looking at their
behavioral patterns you can also do so
by looking at who else is selling
similar products to the people in your
industry that you work with and then
there's another book that I love it's
called The Ultimate Sales letter right
here by Dan
Kennedy and if you can understand this
about your Target customer what keeps
them awake at night what are they afraid
of what are they angry about what are
their top three daily frustrations what
trends are occurring in their life in
their business what do they secretly
desire more than anything else is there
any built-in bias in the way they make
decisions do they have their own
language are there similar products that
are out there and who else has tried
selling to them and failed and when you
understand this you can learn how to
create offers that persuade them to give
you their contact information now the
goal is not simply getting the contact
information from people so that's how
you find people is you create a piece of
content whether it be a video a short
video a long video and you can either do
it organically or you can run ads but
the goal is this to get them on an email
list to get them visit your website and
then you can start to engage with them
to present to them something now one of
the things that I love is
this it's and it's a little secret hack
that most people don't know about when
it comes to paid advert iing is that if
you can get somebody to visit a
website okay so we have
website visits or watch a video so if
they can watch a video that you've
created like this video right here or
they're watching a video that's on your
social media you can then run paid
ads at a nearly
95% discount
and save a ton of money by running
what's called retargeting ads to people
who already visited your website or
watch the video so my goal is this if I
can get somebody watching my video
content consistently if I can get
somebody clicking over to my website
engaging with my social media you can
also do yes social media engagement
that's another one they're literally
just watching your content they're just
clicking they're liking they're
subscribing stuff like that I can run
ads
on YouTube uh Facebook Instagram Tik Tok
LinkedIn at a a generally a 90 to 95%
discount to these people because they
engaged in some way so my goal is this
is I want to what's called
pixel I want to Pixel People and get
them into a bucket that's on the
platforms that says okay they showed
some kind of an interest in the topic
that I'm talking about show them an
ad for something that's going to bribe
them to give me their contact
information or their email address and
what we do is we do a simultaneous bribe
process where we're not only going to
find them but we're also going to
present to them at the same time and we
actually end up combining step one and
step two okay so we create something
that actually delivers something of
value to
people and we're not only going to find
them we're also going to present to them
in the same thing okay and what they're
going to do is they're going to give us
their email address SL text message
information we're going to retarget
maybe a a a small paid ad to them to
find them they might see it through
content and this becomes a loop that
goes back and forth until they join us
on a presentation of some kind so a Pres
presentation this is where you actually
present the thing that you have for sale
and this is the part again like I said
95% of people never do this they do this
whole thing where they'll grow their
email list and they'll they'll find
people through social media they'll
create content they'll create videos
they'll do all this they'll get
followers but they never make a single
sale because they're unwilling to
actually
present in an effective way what it is
that they have for sale they're merely
talking or providing
information but they're not actually
selling to people and so I didn't
actually use the word sell but really
what you're doing here is you are
selling you are making a presentation
that is going to get somebody to see
okay this is for sale we're there's
something for you to buy here you know
for instance my coaching program right
here at the time of this recording we've
charged 200 $ a month to be a part of
this which I think is an extremely
valuable as far as that goes it's it's
extremely affordable and the value that
you get is above and beyond people told
us they spent over 25 grand for other
coaching programs that don't even
scratch the surface as to what we cover
here in our program right here that's
extremely affordable for people okay so
but what you have to do is you have
to present and sell to people what you
have for sale or you're not going to
make any money nobody's going to know
about it expecting people it's a
romantic idea oh I'm just going to
expect them to go to my website and
they're going to go find my stuff that I
have for sale and they're going to go
click and they're going to follow me and
they're going to suddenly see what I
have for sale no
M it's about learning how to communicate
be a powerful
Communicator that persuades people to
take action and when you can learn
persuasion you can learn about cre
creating an
environment that gets people to buy to
where it becomes irresistible to them to
purchase what you have for
sale it's a
process just like dating if you're going
out there and dating you're going to go
find a date right but then you have to
actually close the deal and so the
presentation might be the first or
second date right here but you're not
closing the deal they're not your
boyfriend or girlfriend
you haven't proposed yet okay so that's
where we go into the third phase which
is the close and this is where you
follow up this is where you you have
confidence and you ask for a financial
exchange of some kind without being
timid without hesitating without
worrying about are they going to reject
me do they think that all I care about
is money I don't want to look like one
of those people that all they care about
is money
you got to stop thinking that way you
got to stop stop operating that way in
your mind and realize that the only way
that you will have a business is
learning how to present and sell to
people now we might make another video
where I talk about this process but the
biggest reason why most people will not
present and close sales is because
they're afraid of what everybody thinks
about them they're afraid of
disappointing other people they're
afraid that they're not good enough and
they're processing through their mind is
talking them out of doing the things
that are actually
effective so you have to learn the
skill as well as the knowledge and then
you have to put structure to it to be
able to present sell and close to the
people that you have
found that are on your email list and
this whole process is the ecosystem that
most people refer to as a sales funnel
okay and so that's exactly what we work
with people through in my accelerator
program is how to create effective sales
funnels top to bottom how do you go from
finding them to presenting to closing
okay the first stage of this is learning
how to write good sales
copy how to explain what you're doing
well to
people as well as working on what is
between your two ears that is preventing
you from showing up confidently at each
stage of this process what is preventing
you from having
total
confidence that you can help somebody
and you're not afraid
of what happens
next you're not holding back because
you're
unsure you might say well Jeremiah if I
did all the right things then I would be
unsure can I I can I tell you this I
meet people all the time they're right
where you
are and then they waste five years 10
years talking themselves out of even
setting up this
process talking themselves out of
putting themselves out
there and they
got many angry reasons why they get
angry about it as to why they're just
not ready yet to do
it we got to upgrade
ourselves we got to go to the next level
and realize that what we've been doing
up to this moment in time isn't working
and that to be able to do this requires
us to step
into a new way of being showing up
communicating
having boundaries and believing in
ourselves and if you don't believe in
yourself nobody else is going
to
okay so when you put this together how
do you find these
people you have to have some kind
of
a
offer so this is your offer right here
and you need to have an offer letter
so the offer letter you show to people
and then they read your offer letter and
they
decide yes or no pretty simple what is a
yes or a no to an offer letter A yes is
they give you their email address they
sign up they give you their contact info
they put it in their calendar to join
you to listen to you a no is they go
about their life and they go watch
Netflix for the next 10
hours pretty
simple you can't change a no into a yes
but you want to figure out who these
yeses are and find more of them and
that's where we end up tweaking the
words that are written in this offer
letter and as we optimize that which is
exactly what I work with people on in
the client growth accelerator is how to
we optimize your offer letter to get
more of the right yes people that are
your true people people that you want to
work with your true followers your true
fans the ones who are completely
connected with you that will buy into
whatever it is that you have to
offer and you just continue
communicating with
them and you end up serving them and you
learn how to sell to them effectively in
a way where you show up with total
confidence total total belief in what
you're doing and you figure out what do
I got to shift in my life to make that
happen what do I got to adjust in my
life what levers do I need to start to
pull to make that actually come
together you might not be there today
most people who join my program are not
there today when they
start but we can get you there and we
can work with you through that process
and we can help you so that you have
Clarity so that you know exactly what
steps to take so that you know exactly
how to write the right offer letters so
that you know what to put on your social
media so that you know how to
communicate and sell and present in a
way that actually gets people to buy
instead of waste your time and their
time what are the words that you say
what are the words that you put in your
emails how do you follow up with people
what do you do if maybe things are
working and then they don't after all as
far as that goes this
happens that's what I Mentor people on
every single week I'd love to help you
with that as well okay so what you got
to learn how to do is make more offers
we got an event coming up very soon
you'll start to see it on my social
media if you don't follow me on
Instagram or Facebook or all that go
look up my name on those platforms go
follow me on there go literally right
now go go pull out your phone right now
and go look
up Jeremiah Kowski or you can look up
Jeremy crack that's the name right there
Jeremy
crack on Instagram you'll see my the
orange photo right there you can follow
me on Instagram right here okay you can
go type in my name on Facebook you can
subscribe to this channel as well and
you will see see when we have an event
where I'm going to work with you through
coming up how to put an offer together
okay here's me right there as well on on
Facebook this is very possible for you
and when you learn how to do this you
don't have to work 110 hours a week I
don't want you
to I don't want you to have to work 110
hours a
week I think to be able to bring in the
kind of money that you want to make you
can do so while only
working 10 to 15 hours a week to make
10,000 15,000 $25,000 a month doing this
process but it's going to take some
growth it's going to take learning some
new methods learning some new skills
learning how to do some things that
maybe you've never done before and I'm
here to help you through that process
and I'd love to work with you and I'd
love to walk alongside you come
alongside you become a part of your team
to make this happen for you all right
listen thanks for watching this video
make sure to subscribe to the channel
make sure to get on the waiting list for
our client growth accelerator program so
that when we do open the doors to this
you can get on the fast track to making
the kind of results that you want to
make in your business so you can finally
have the income and the
impact that you want to
have my name is jeremi Kowski we'll see
you on the next video talk to soon